realtytimes.com 2013-06-30

# Privacy Statement

| 

Privacy Statement 

### The Information We Collect

At the Realty Times website, you can order products, enter contests, vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion, subscribe to one of our services such as our online newsletters, or participate in one of our online forums. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages include: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, credit card information, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services. 

At some other Realty Times sites, you may submit information about other people. For example, you might submit a person's name and e-mail address to send an electronic newsletter and want it sent directly to the recipient, you might submit the recipient's name and email address. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected about other people at these pages may include: recipient's name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number. 

We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows '95 or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink). 

### How We Use the Information

We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, and to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you. 

We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to notify you when we make changes to our subscriber agreements, to provide some news or points of interest, to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter, or to contact you about your account with us. 

The information we collect in connection with our online forums and communities is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums and communities and, from time to time, to offer you products, programs, or services. 

If you choose to submit content for publication (e.g., a "letter to our editors"), we may publish your screen name and other information you have provided to us. 

We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services. 

We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request, or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. In addition, we may transfer information about you if we are acquired by or merged with another company. 

Agents and contractors of Realty Times who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for Realty Times. 

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Notice. 

We may on occasion combine information we receive online with outside records to enhance our ability to market to you those products or services that may be of interest to you. If you prefer not to receive marketing information from this site, click here for instructions on how to make your request. 

Finally, the Realty Times site covered by this Privacy Notice will not use or transfer personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt out of these unrelated uses. 

### Cookies & Web Beacons

To enhance your experience with our sites, many of our web pages use "cookies." Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one of our sites. However, once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie. 

We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to our site), save your password in password-protected areas, and enable you to use shopping carts on our sites. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services. 

"Web beacons" or clear .gifs are small pieces of code placed on a web page to monitor the behavior and collect data about the visitors viewing a web page. For example, web beacons can be used to count the users who visit a web page or to deliver a cookie to the browser of a visitor viewing that page. We may use web beacons on this site from time to time for this and other purposes. 

### Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites, Ad Servers, and Sponsors

Advertisers on Realty Times contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties. 

The Realty Times site covered by this Privacy Notice sometimes may offer content (e.g., contests, sweepstakes, or promotions) that is sponsored by or cobranded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the site activity. Realty Times has no control over these third parties' use of this information. The Realty Times site will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if these third parties will obtain such information. 

Some of the Realty Times site covered by this Privacy Notice may use a reputable third party to present or serve the advertisements that you may see at its Web pages. These third party ad servers may use cookies, web beacons, clear .gifs or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements' effectiveness. The use of these technologies by these third party ad servers is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by our privacy policy. 

### Our Commitment to Security

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online. 

How You can Access or Correct Information For instructions on how you can access the personally identifiable information that Realty Times site has collected about you online, or how to correct factual errors in such information, please click here. To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. 

### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about the Realty Times online policy for this site or its implementation you may contact us at [privacy@RealtyTimes.com](mailto:privacy@RealtyTimes.com?subject=Privacy). 

### Updates & Effective Date

From time to time, we may update this privacy notice. We will notify you about material changes in the way we treat personally identifiable information by placing a notice on our site. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it. 

The Privacy Notice posted on this site was updated on or about August 15, 2011. 

|    

Real Estate News Network

**Mortgage Rates**  
30 Year Fixed: 3.98%  
15 Year Fixed: 3.10%  
1 Year Adj: 2.58%  
(U.S. Weekly Averages)  

Today's Headlines 08/10/2006  

  * Get The Facts, Stop Mosquito Attacks
  * Home-Selling Strategy
  * California Property Tax System Coming Under Fire
  * Must See Custom Model Home On 2 Acres In Almont, MI
  * Report Deflates Bubble Talk With Subdued Housing Forecast
  * Feds Send Mortgage Rates Into Uncertain Territory
  * Knowing Your Soil: The Foundation of a Great Home
  * Agents: Make Your 2nd Half Powerful!
  * Staking an HOA Claim
  * Housing Counsel: Cancellation Does Not Always Mean Cancellation

* * *

Spotlight
